

Over the course of my professional career, I have steadily evolved into a Full-Stack Developer. One of my earliest jobs was as a Graphic Designer, which then led me into Web Development. Over time, I became more interested in back-end programming and advanced my skills through self-study, college education, and experience. This has given me an advantage when it comes to design and development of software applications.

CONTACT

11.98110.6960

david.r.gully@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/davidgully

Santo André - SP, Brasil

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree

Computer Information Systems Valdosta State University 2013 – 2014

Computer Science
University of Central Florida
2000 – 2002

SKILLS

Professional

Project Management Software Engineering Web Development User Experience Digital Marketing

Technical

HTML, CSS, JavaScript .NET, C#, VB, Java, PHP SQL, MySQL, MongoDB IIS, AWS, Azure

AWARDS

Outstanding CIS Student Scholarship

Valdosta State University Georgia / USA / April 2014

Published: Self-Driving Vehicles

Omnino, VSU Undergrad Georgia / USA / November 2014

Recognized for Exemplary Service

US Navy, Divert Support, E15 NAVSTA Rota / Spain / May 2010

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Critical Network Solutions / 2020 - Present

Full-stack development of custom web apps for our clients. Responsible for every aspect of the software development process – all the way from initial requirements gathering to on-the-spot maintenance. Also, in charge of managing each project and keeping clients informed. Latest project is development of a SPA on Azure using Blazor server-side.

Director of Information Technology

The Christian Family Center / 2019 - 2020

Responsibilities included the management and optimization of IT resources, establishing and monitoring security protocols, maintenance scheduling, general training, and supervision of employees' resource usage. Redesigned the website and integration of social media platforms. Managed the reorganization and privileges of sensitive documents to remain HIPAA compliant. Instrumental in the facility re-certification process by ensuring preparation and procuring all required documents.

Software Engineer

Nexxtep Technology Services / 2014 - 2019

Managed and participated in the development and maintenance of software applications built using various programming languages, but primarily .NET. Additionally, oversaw the improvement of existing applications that were already in use and maintained legacy code. Met directly with clients for requirements gathering, job quoting, project planning, troubleshooting, and delivery. Supervised interns, assigned tasks, tutored, and code reviewed.

Back-End Developer

Ascend Inbound Marketing / 2016 - 2019

Developed API integrations for e-commerce websites built using the following technologies: HubSpot, WordPress, WooCommerce, Stitch Labs, Ship Station, Shopify, Zapier, and Databox. Custom HubL, ASP, PHP, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL, SQL, JSON, XML. Middleware creation, modification and communication, OAuth and security implementation.

Computer Science Tutor

Valdosta State University / 2013 - 2014

Responsibilities included one-on-one interaction and instruction of various Computer Science subjects ranging from basic computer programming in Java to upper-level theory and concepts. Also, in charge of facilitating a weekly hour-long help session for the introductory programming courses.

VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES

American Red Cross

Valdosta, Georgia 2017 – 2019

Hands on Network

Statesboro, Georgia